# MANUELA FERNANDEZ

FRONTEND DEVELOPER / MECHANICAL ENGINEER





### CONTACT

Email: mafernandezgo@hotmail.com

Phone: (+57) 313 794 8111



@mafernandezgo

**GO TO MY PORTFOLIO** 



# **SKILLS**

- Strategic Planning
- Self-Taught Person
- Eficiency
- Communication
- Logical Reasoning
- Proactivity
- Self Management



**LANGUAGES** 

**English** 

### **PROFILE**

Mechanical Engineer with 4 years of experience in engineering projects development, budgets, coordination and management of work team activities.

For the last half year, she has been dedicated exclusively to **web development**, gaining knowledge on Html, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript y React.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# **Projects Engineer**

OSHO Ingenieria | 2017 - 2021

- 1. Development of conceptual, basic and detailed engineering based on local and international regulations (NFPA).
- 2. Coordination of activities of the engineering assistants for the development of the project.
- 3. Review of design plans, installation details, calculation results and information coding.

# **Engineer Internship**

## Ecopetrol | 2016 - 2017

- 1. Preparation of inventory focused on artificial lifting equipment distributed in the production field.
- 2. Management and implementation of the maintenance plan for progressive cavity pumps (PCP).
- 3. Set and sizing of stock for maintenance.

### **EDUCATION**



Make it Real

Full Stack JS Web Developer | 2021



Universidad Nacional de Colombia

Mechanical Engineer | 2011 - 2017

# MANUELA FERNANDEZ

DESARROLLADORA FRONTEND / INGENIERA MECÁNICA





### CONTACTO

Email: mafernandezgo@hotmail.com

Celular: (+57) 313 794 8111





IR A MI PORTAFOLIO



# **HABILIDADES**

- Planificación
- Autodidacta
- Eficiencia
- Comunicación Asertiva
- Razonamiento Lógico
- Proactividad
- Autogestión



**IDIOMAS** 

**Ingles** 

### **PERFIL**

Ingeniera Mecánica con 4 años de experiencia en desarrollo de proyectos de ingeniería, presupuestos, coordinación y gestión de actividades en equipos de trabajo. Durante los últimos 6 meses se ha dedicado exclusivamente al desarrollo web, adquiriendo conocimientos en HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript y React.

### **EXPERIENCIA LABORAL**

## Ingeniera de Proyectos

OSHO Ingenieria | 2017 - 2021

- 1. Desarrollo de Ingenierías conceptuales, básicas y de detalle basados en normatividad local e internacional (NFPA).
- 2. Coordinación de actividades de los auxiliares de ingeniería para el desarrollo del proyecto.
- 3. Revisión de planos de diseño, detalles de instalación, resultado de calculo y codificación de la información.

## Practicante de Ingeniería

Ecopetrol | 2016 - 2017

- 1. Elaboración de inventario enfocado a los equipos de levantamiento artificial distribuidos en campo.
- 2.Gestión e implementación del plan de mantenimiento para las bombas de cavidades progresivas (PCP).
- 3. Caracterización y dimensionamiento del stock para el mantenimiento.

# FORMACIÓN ACADÉMICA



Make it Real

Full Stack | S Web Developer | 2021



Universidad Nacional de Colombia

Ingenieria Mecánica | 2011 - 2017